Guide to the Pierre Hohenberg, Deputy Provost for Science and Technology, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- General and individual departmental files, 1980-2001; Accession 2006-A-178
  - Retirement
    - 2002 (Box 5, Folder 202)
    - 2001 (Box 5, Folder 203)
  - Sachem Ventures, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 204)
  - Sandia National Labs, 2001 April 13 (Box 5, Folder 205)
  - Scholar Awards Committee, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 206)
  - Science Hill
    - General, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 209)
    - Rollout, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 210)
  - Research
    - Admin Yale, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 211)
    - Compliance, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 212)
    - COGR, 2000 September 30 (Box 6, Folder 213)
    - DARPA, 2000 September 20 (Box 6, Folder 214)
    - Equipment Transfer, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 215)
    - Federal, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 216)
    - Human Subjects, 2000 July 17 (Box 6, Folder 217)
    - Issues, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 218)
    - Officers-- Meeting, 1999-2001 (Box 6, Folder 219 - 220)
    - Organization, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 221)
    - Postdocs, 1999-2001 (Box 6, Folder 222)
    - PI Reports, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 223)
    - Strategies, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 224)
    - YARC, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 225)
  - Shops, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 226)
  - Slots, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 227)
  - SMARTS, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 228)
  - STARS, 2001 November 15 (Box 6, Folder 229)
  - Studies, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 230)
  - Tax Rules, 2000 November 7 (Box 6, Folder 231)
  - Team Lux, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 232)
  - Tercentennial, 2000 August 30 (Box 6, Folder 234)
  - Topical Biology Association, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 235)
  - UCAR, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 236)
  - VIGRE, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 237)
  - Women in Science, 1999-2001 (Box 6, Folder 238)
  - Yale-- Chile, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 239)
  - Yale- China, 2000 May 24 (Box 6, Folder 240)
  - Yale College
    - 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 241)
    - HHMI, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 242)
    - Science Courses, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 243)
    - STARS, 2001 October 1 (Box 7, Folder 244)
  - Yale Institutional Info, 2000 April 11 (Box 7, Folder 245)
  - Yale Science Forum, 2001 April 19 (Box 7, Folder 246)
  - Yale University
    - Administration, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 247)
    - Administration/Reaccredidation, 2000 February 1 (Box 7, Folder 248)
    - Archival Schedule, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 249)
    - Honorary Degrees, 2001 November 12 (Box 7, Folder 250)
    - Policies-- Med School, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 251)
  - Yale Inst. for Biospheric Studies (YIBS)
    - Bass Chair, 1990-1999 (Box 7, Folder 252)
    - YIBS CEP, 2001 October 30 (Box 7, Folder 253)
    - General, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 254)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 255)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 256)
    - Population Center, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 257)
    - Summer, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 258)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 259)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 260)
    - CCE Endowment, 1998 March 12 (Box 7, Folder 261)
    - Biosphere, 1998 April 2 (Box 7, Folder 262)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 263)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 264)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 265)
  - YSEA, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 266)
- Deputy provost for science and technology records, 1974-2004; Accession 2008-A-150
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2040
  - AAU, 2002 May 15 - 2003 August 29 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Cmte of the Div of Phys Sciences, 2003 August 13 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Andes, 2003 July 31 - October 20 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Animal Facilities
    - Central Campus Animal Study, 2001 November 7 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - YARC, 2001 September 6 - 2003 April 8 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Anthro Building, 2003 September 19 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Assistant Provost, 2003 June (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Astro OBS
    - 2003-2004, 2003 July 21- September 15 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 2002-03, 2002 August 6 - November 11 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Beckman, 2003 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Benefits, 2003 July 29 - 2004 June 22 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Bioenformatics, 2003 November - December 15 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Biomedical Engineering
    - 2003-2004, 2003 August 22 - September 30 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Faculty of Engineering, 2001 December 6 - 2003 May 16 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Biomedical Program, 9 July 2002 - 27 May 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 2002-2003, 9 July 2002 19 June 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 2003 December 5 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Centers
    - CT Aerospace Institute, 2002 January 25 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Astron and Astrophysics, 2001 August 1 - 2002 November 3 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Bush Center, 2002 June 2 - 2003 March 7 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - CTR For Study of Globalization, 2002 April 10 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Cognitive Neuroimaging (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - CTR for Earth Observation (CEO), 2002 February 26 - 2002 October (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Quantum info, 2002 December 30 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Peking Yale, 2002 November 25 - January 25 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Genomics and Proteomics CTR, 2002 April 30 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Child Scholarship Benefit, 2003 July 29 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Classroom Study, 2002 January 2 - 19 July (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - CEO, 2003 August 29 - September 8 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - CESOF 2003-2004, 2003 September 18 - October 17 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - COI 2003-2004, 2003 January 30 - December 9 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Committees 2003-2004, 28 May 2003 - 2 October (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - COMPRES 2003, 10 April 2003 - 19 November (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Cooperative Research, 2002 March 12 - November 5 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Corporate Partners Program
    - 2003 Sep 19 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - 2001 Jul - 2002 Aug (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Corporate Relations, 2003 July 28 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Corporation
    - 2003 Jan 13 -Dec 22 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Planning, 2003 September 30 - October 3 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Ford, 2002 October 23 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - IBM, 11 October 2002 - 26 February 2003 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Monsanto, 2002 June 26 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Pitney/Bowes, 10 July 2002 - 18 December (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Merck, 2003 January 6 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Pfizer, 2003 April 27 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - COSSA, 2003 March 17 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - DSSG, 2003 February 27 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - DOE 2003, 2003 November 12 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Development
    - 2003, 2003 May 7- 22 December (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Indiv Donors/Asteroids, 2003 January 22 - 17 September (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Diversity, Summer 2002 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Divisional Budget, 2002 April 30 - 2003 June 19 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Energy 2003, 2003 November 26 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - FOE
    - 2003, 2003 August 18 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Budget FY03, 2002 January 31 - 2003 June 9 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Strategic Plan, Fall 2003 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Environment Eng. Fellowships, 2003 August 14 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - ESC Steering Committee, 2003 January 7 - 2004 January 8 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Export Controls, 2003 September 1 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Faculty Activity Reports, Fall 2003 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Faculty Renewal Funds, 2003 July 25 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Gates: Grand-Challenges, 2003 May 30 - August 7 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - General Counsel, 2003 October 28 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Genomics Initiative
    - General, 2002 January 31 - April 24 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Executive Summary, 2001 November 9 - 2002 March 7 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Proposals, 2000 December 19 - 2001 July 6 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Correspondence, 1998 February 2 - 2001 November 15 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Budget, 2001 October 30 - November 27 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Keck Facilities, 1998 October 28 - 2001 September 8 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Gifts, 2003 October 8 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - GS Comm, 2003 January 6 - December 8 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Government, 2003 February 14 - December 4 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Graduate School
    - Complaints, 2003 September 10 - October 16 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Orientation Information, 2003 August 19 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - HHMI
    - Associate Salary, 2003 June 30 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Misc., 2003 June 30 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Professors, 2001 September 12 - 2002 May 1 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Teaching Program, 2002 July 26 (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Misc., 2002 January 23- April 17 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - History of Science, 2003 April 21 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - HPC, 2003 March 6 - August 28 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Human Resources
    - Wages, 2003 September 18 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - IBM, 2003 July 1 - August 11 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - I.F.A.I., 2003 October 6 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Keck Center, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Keck Quantum Info, 2002 December 19 - 2003 December 30 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Labor Negotiation, 2003 September 19 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Lab Policies, 2003 June 27 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Luce Program
    - 2003 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Marsh Garden
    - 2003 (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - 2002 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Moore, 2003 March 11 - September 15 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Morse-JFF Recipients, 2003 October 13 - 23 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Named Professorship Policy, 1997 July 1 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - National SEC COMM, 2003 November 17 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Next Economy Partners, 2002 March 15 - April 25 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - NIH, 2003 August 29 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - NSF/Faculties Survey
    - NSF 2003 Facilities (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - 2003, 2003 December 15 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - NSF Instrumentation Awards, 2003 December 4-5 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - NSF/MRI, 2003 October 28 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - OCR, 2002 January 27 - 2004 August 20 (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - OEHS, 2003 December 8 (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - Omega-P, 2003 July 31 (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - ONSAGER, 2003 January 22 - October 7 (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - Operating Budget, 2002 February 22 - 2003 April 4 (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - OSTP 2003, 1905 June 25 (Box 3, Folder 142)
  - Peabody Museum
    - 2003 Jul 1 -Dec 8 (Box 3, Folder 143)
    - Budget, 2003 September 26 - December 1 (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - Development, 2003 May 27 (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - Endowments, 2003 September 2 - October 17 (Box 3, Folder 146)
  - Physical Science Division, 2003 June 19 (Box 3, Folder 147)
  - PostDocs
    - 2003 Jul 2 - Oct 13 (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - Office 2003-2004, 2003 June 25 - November 25 (Box 3, Folder 149)
  - Prizes and Awards, 2003 January 15 - April 3 (Box 3, Folder 150)
  - Proposals -- Packard, 2003 January 17 - April 1 (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - Provost Responsibilites, 2003 August 8 (Box 3, Folder 152)
  - Purchase Requisitions, 2003 July 2 - 10 (Box 3, Folder 153)
  - Quinnipiack Club, 2003 September 1 (Box 3, Folder 154)
  - Recommendation Letters, 2003 October 30 - December 18 (Box 3, Folder 155)
  - Recruitments, 2003 May 29 (Box 3, Folder 156)
  - Research
    - Indirect Costs, 2003 April 1 (Box 3, Folder 157)
    - Strategies, 2003 March 23 (Box 3, Folder 158)
    - YARC, 2002 March 11 - June 18 (Box 3, Folder 159)
  - Salaries, 2003 May 16 - September 1 (Box 3, Folder 160)
  - Science Hill Rollout, 2003 April 24 (Box 3, Folder 163)
  - General, 2003 September 26 (Box 3, Folder 164)
  - Science and Nat'l Security, 2003 February 7 - September 26 (Box 3, Folder 165)
  - SR. Faculty Fellowships, 2003 July 19 (Box 3, Folder 166)
  - SRO, 2003 April - November 11 (Box 3, Folder 167)
  - Sigma Xi, 2003 June 26 (Box 3, Folder 168)
  - Slots, 20 January 2003 - 9 November 2003 (Box 3, Folder 169)
  - Slot Reports, 2003 September 3 (Box 3, Folder 170)
  - Smarts, 2003 April 22 - 24 (Box 3, Folder 171)
  - Space, 2003 March 1 (Box 3, Folder 172)
  - Hester Vanderhoer/Learning Center, 2003 May 13 (Box 3, Folder 173)
  - Strike Info, 2003 February 21 - August 20 (Box 3, Folder 174)
  - Sustainable Food Project, 2003 August 13 - December 18 (Box 3, Folder 175)
  - Teaching Equipment, 2003 May 7 (Box 3, Folder 176)
  - Teaching Labs, 2003 March 31 - May 6 (Box 3, Folder 177)
  - Telephones, 2003 August 15 (Box 3, Folder 178)
  - Travel, 2003 January 15 (Box 3, Folder 179)
  - Unsuccessful Searches, 2003 January 8 (Box 3, Folder 180)
  - Vigre, 2003 January 13- September 2 (Box 3, Folder 181)
  - Website, 2003 September 26 (Box 3, Folder 182)
  - Women In Science, 2003 April 3 - November 8 (Box 3, Folder 183)
  - Woodrow Wilson Fellowship, 2003 October 1 (Box 3, Folder 184)
  - Yale-Peking, 2003 October 23-24 (Box 3, Folder 185)
  - Yale/History
    - 2008 Sep 3 (Box 3, Folder 186)
    - 2002 Oct 14 (Box 3, Folder 187)
  - Yale School of Nursing, Summer 2003 (Box 3, Folder 188)
  - YIBS
    - 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 189)
    - 2003-2004 Budget, 2003 November 17 (Box 3, Folder 190)
    - 2003-2004 Faculty Council, 2004 January 29 - September 30 (Box 3, Folder 191)
    - 2003-2004 Fund for Centers, 2003 April 13 - November 4 (Box 3, Folder 192)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 193)
    - 2002-2003 CEO, 2002 September 27 (Box 3, Folder 194)
    - 2002-2003 Imortant Docs, 1997 March 12 - 2003 June 13 (Box 3, Folder 195)
    - 2003-2003 Slots, 2002 December 19 (Box 3, Folder 196)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 3)
    - 2001-2002 CEO, 2002 February 26 (Box 3, Folder 197)
    - 2001-2002 Slots, 2002 April 26 (Box 3, Folder 198)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 199)
  - YSM NIH Instrument Grant, 2003 September 8 (Box 3, Folder 200)
  - Facilities
    - Annual Bldg Consumption, 2002 January 30 (Box 4, Folder 201)
    - 1996 Jun 15 -2001 Oct 10 (Box 4, Folder 202)
    - Science Hill Planning, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 203)
    - General, 1995- 2003 (Box 4, Folder 204 - 206)
    - Benchmark, 2002 April 12 (Box 4, Folder 207)
    - Eng-Dunham, 1996 - 2002 (Box 4, Folder 208 - 209)
    - EEB, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 210)
    - 175 Whitney Avenue, 1995- 2001 (Box 4, Folder 211)
    - 370 Temple Street, 1994- 2000 (Box 4, Folder 212)
    - 89/87 Trumball, 2002 July 18 (Box 4, Folder 213)
    - Anthropology, 2001 - 2003 (Box 4, Folder 214)
    - Chemistry
      - 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 215)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 216)
      - Research Bldg, 2001 November (Box 4, Folder 217)
    - Engineering
      - ESC Steering, 2002 - 2003 (Box 4, Folder 218)
      - Cleanroom, 1996- 2000 (Box 4, Folder 219)
      - Mason Lab, 1998- 2003 (Box 4, Folder 220)
      - Gibbs, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 221)
      - KBT, 2000- 2001 (Box 4, Folder 222 - 223)
      - KGL, 1999- 2000 (Box 4, Folder 224)
      - OML, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 225)
      - Phys-Astro, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 226)
    - FAS Acq., 2002 August 14 (Box 4, Folder 227)
    - Environmental Focus Group, 1993- 2000 (Box 4, Folder 228)
    - Env Green Plan, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 229)
    - Chem Bldg Comm, 1997- 2002 (Box 5, Folder 230)
    - MCDB
      - Facilities MRB, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 231)
    - Pierson Sage Garage, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 232)
    - Sloane, 1995- 2002 (Box 5, Folder 233)
    - Space
      - Info, 2000 February 15 (Box 5, Folder 234)
      - Surveys, 2001 March 7 (Box 5, Folder 235)
    - Proposals, 2001 October 25 (Box 5, Folder 236)
    - UPLAN, 2000-2002 (Box 5, Folder 237)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences (FAS)
    - Appointment Procedures, 1989- 2002 (Box 5, Folder 238)
    - Budget
      - 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 239)
      - Planning, 2001-2003 (Box 5, Folder 240)
      - 2000-2002 (Box 5, Folder 241)
      - 2000 (Box 5, Folder 242)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 243)
      - 2000-2002 (Box 5, Folder 244)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 245)
    - Business Affair, 2002 September 11 (Box 5, Folder 246)
    - Chair Compensation, 1998- 2000 (Box 5, Folder 247)
    - Committee on Tenure Appts, 1999- 2000 (Box 5, Folder 248)
    - Expanded Executive Committee, 2001 November 14 (Box 5, Folder 249)
    - Faculty Activity Reports, 1999- 2002 (Box 5, Folder 250)
    - Faculty/Burch, 2002 September 9 (Box 5, Folder 251)
    - HPC Background, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 252)
    - Interdisciplinary Dept, 1999- 2000 (Box 5, Folder 253)
    - Moving, 2003 April 8 (Box 5, Folder 254)
    - Nonladder FAC, 1999 October 6 - 2001 April 25 (Box 5, Folder 255)
    - Other, 1998- 2002 (Box 5, Folder 256)
    - Faculty Affairs, 2000- 2002 (Box 5, Folder 257)
    - Language Faculty, 2000 April 14 (Box 5, Folder 259)
    - Peer Institute Data, 1999- 2001 (Box 5, Folder 260)
    - Retirements, 2002 December 20 (Box 5, Folder 261)
  - Departments
    - Anthropology
      - 2002 (Box 6, Folder 262)
      - 2001- 2002 (Box 6, Folder 263)
      - 2001 (Box 6, Folder 264)
    - Applied Phsyics
      - 2002-03 (Box 6, Folder 265)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 266)
    - Astronomy
      - 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 267)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 268)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 269)
    - Astrophysics, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 270)
    - Chemistry
      - 2003-2004, 2001 October 22 (Box 6, Folder 271)
      - Dept File 2002-03, 2003 January 29 (Box 6, Folder 272)
      - Dept File 2000-2001, 2001 April 24 (Box 6, Folder 273)
      - Research Bldg, July 2002 - 31 October 2003 (Box 6, Folder 274)
      - Building, 3 April 2001 - March 2003 (Box 6, Folder 275)
    - Computer Science
      - 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 276)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 277)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 278)
    - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology
      - Projects, 2003 December 10 (Box 6, Folder 279)
      - Renovations, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 280)
      - 2002-03 (Box 6, Folder 281)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 282)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 283)
      - Review, 2003 (Box 6)
    - Electrical Engineering, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 284)
    - Environmental Eng, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 285)
    - Faculty of Engineering
      - Computer Engineering, 1998 August 25 (Box 6, Folder 286)
      - Non Ladder, 2000-2003 (Box 6, Folder 287)
      - Pamphlets, 1994-1995 (Box 6)
      - Engineering Graduate Student Support, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 289)
      - Dean Search, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 290)
      - Dept-Vision (Box 6, Folder 291)
      - Team Lux, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 292)
      - 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 293)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 294)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 295)
      - Students, 2001 - 2003 (Box 6, Folder 296)
      - Development, 2001-2003 (Box 6, Folder 297)
      - Annual Reports, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 298)
    - Geology and Geophysics
      - 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 299)
      - 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 300)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 301)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 302)
      - Recruits, 2003 November 13 (Box 6, Folder 303)
      - Unsuccessful Recruit, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 304)
      - Computing (Box 6, Folder 305)
    - Linguistics
      - 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 306)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 307)
    - Mathematics
      - Development, 2000 June 26 (Box 6, Folder 308)
      - Math Positions, 2000 September 13 (Box 6, Folder 309)
      - Gibbs, 2000 2001 (Box 6, Folder 310)
      - Math Rebates, 1998- 2000 (Box 6, Folder 311)
      - 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 312)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 313)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 314)
    - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry
      - 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 316)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 317)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 318)
      - Building, 2003 November 14 (Box 6, Folder 319)
      - Administration, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 320)
      - Advanced Photon Source/ MOU, 2000- 2002 (Box 6, Folder 321)
      - Audit, 2003 January 19 (Box 6, Folder 322)
    - Molecular, Cellular and Developmental Biology
      - 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 324)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 325)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 326)
      - Unsuccessful, 2002 April 24 (Box 6, Folder 327)
      - Building, 1999-2003 (Box 6, Folder 329 - 330)
    - Mechanical Engineering
      - 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 331)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 332)
      - Searches, 2003 August 4 (Box 6, Folder 333)
      - Unsuccessful 2001, 2001 April 20 (Box 6, Folder 334)
    - Peabody Museum
      - 2002-03 (Box 6, Folder 335)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 336)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 337)
    - Physics
      - 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 338)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 339)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 340)
      - IT, 2003 November 26 (Box 7, Folder 341)
      - Unsuccesful Search 2002, 2002 May 2 (Box 7, Folder 342)
      - Fall Mtng, 1999- 2000 (Box 7, Folder 343)
    - Statistics
      - 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 344)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 345)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 346)
      - Statistics Initiative, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 347)
  - FES
    - 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 348 - 349)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 350)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 351)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 352)
    - Admin/Data, 2002 October 1 (Box 7, Folder 354)
    - Dean, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 355)
    - Admin-Staff Salaries, 1999- 2002 (Box 7, Folder 356)
    - Assessments, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 357)
    - Budget, 2001-2003 (Box 7, Folder 358)
    - Building, 2002- 2003 (Box 7, Folder 359)
    - Curriculum, 1992- 2001 (Box 7, Folder 360)
    - Development (Box 7)
    - Development, 1995- 2002 (Box 7, Folder 361)
    - Dev - Leadership Council, 2001 February 16 (Box 7, Folder 362)
    - Facilities: FES BLDG, 1998-2003 (Box 7, Folder 363)
    - Facil/ 230 Prospect, 2002 November 13 (Box 7, Folder 364)
    - Faculty Affairs
      - 1999- 2002 (Box 7, Folder 365)
      - Faculty, 2002- 2003 (Box 7, Folder 366)
      - Salaries, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 367)
      - Appointments, 2000-2002 (Box 7, Folder 368)
    - Green Power, 2003 September 23 (Box 7, Folder 369)
    - Journal, 2002- 2003 (Box 7, Folder 370)
    - Misc Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 371)
    - NY Botanical Garden, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 372)
    - Planning Study - New Bldg, 1999- 2001 (Box 7, Folder 373)
    - Proposals
      - FES Proposals, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 374)
      - Ford FDN, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 375)
      - Moore, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 376)
    - PSPP Documentation, 13 February 2000 - 4 April 2002 (Box 7, Folder 377)
    - Research -- Memo of Understanding, 25 April 96 - 12 November 2001 (Box 7, Folder 378)
    - SAAC
      - 2002-2003, 2003 July 9 (Box 7, Folder 379)
      - 1992- 2002 (Box 7, Folder 380)
      - Dept/ SAC General Plan, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 381)
    - Search Procedures
      - Searches, 7 October 96 - 18 September 2002 (Box 7, Folder 382)
      - Weyerhauser Chair, 17 January 96 - 19 April 96 (Box 7, Folder 383)
      - Student Affairs, 4 December 2000 - 26 February 2003 (Box 7, Folder 384)
      - Water Museum, May 2002 - 11 July 2002 (Box 7, Folder 385)
  - FOE Dean Search
    - CMTE meeting 5-14-07, 2007 May 14 (Box 8, Folder 386)
    - CMTE meeting 5-7-07, 2007 April 30 (Box 8, Folder 387)
    - meeting 4-30-07, 2007 April 9 - 30 (Box 8, Folder 388)
    - Seach CMTE meering, 2007 April 11- 16 (Box 8, Folder 389)
    - Search meeting, 2007 April 9 (Box 8, Folder 390)
    - CMTE meeting, 2007 March 26 (Box 8, Folder 391)
    - 2006 Jun 14 - Nov 20 (Box 8, Folder 392 - 395)
    - Candidates
      - 2006 Aug 17 (Box 8, Folder 396)
      - Other Candidates, 2006 October 27 - 2007 March 29 (Box 8, Folder 440 - 441)